Hello everyone, welcome to all of you friends.
In this video we are going to see
ICICI Prudential AMC IPO. If we
talk about ICICI Prudential AMC IPO, then
what is the latest update coming out about the allotment status of this IPO,
what kind of message, what kind of
update were you getting, understand that the
allotment has been received and by
when will the allotment status start appearing on the site,
what is the latest GMP visible, we are going to talk about them in
detail in this video.
Watch the video till the end and subscribe to the channel for such
daily IPO grey market premium
updates.
Also, the link to the Telegram group has been given in the comments.  You
can also join there
for timely updates.  First of all,
if you had applied for ICICI Principal AMC IPO on any of these three dates i.e. 12th
of December, 15th of December or 16th of
December,
then today's events should
start showing on the registrar site of this company on 17th of December itself, according to all the guidelines.
But till now the
allotment status has not started appearing on the registrar site of this company.
So if we talk about this IPO here, then
we will discuss further when you will start seeing the allotment status of this IPO.  So
visit the direct registrar site of this company, the
link of Telegram group is given in the comments,
join that group.  There,
as soon as the allotment status starts appearing on the registrar site of this company between 10 to 12 till late night.
Similarly, if you
click on the link that will be shared,
you can directly visit the site with this type of interface.  As soon as you
visit, scroll down.
As soon as you scroll down, you
can see the names of many companies.  In the
same way, if the name of this company
ICICI Prudential LED Company
starts appearing here, then you have to select it.  If the
applicant has a PAN number, then
after entering the PAN number, if you click on submit,
you will get information about whether you got allotment in this IPO
or not.
But if you see the message of bank
debit of ₹14,000, sorry ₹12,990
coming from the bank, then understand that
you have got the allotment in this IPO.   If you are
getting the message of credit and revoke then
understand that you have not got allotment in this IPO.
Or if you have not received any of these messages from the
bank then
wait and watch.  As soon as the
allotment status starts appearing on the registrar site of this company.
Similarly, you
people will be updated by sharing the link.  Well, let's talk about the
latest grey market premium update of this company.
So here its grey
market premium is showing some pressure.
Its grey market premium has reached ₹345.
₹345 will be added on ₹2165.  So if we
talk about the listing price, then for ₹2500
you are getting ₹10 listing price.  There
is a 16% chance of getting listing gains on one lot.  The
IPO is seen giving you listing gains in the coming time around ₹2070.
Further,
whatever update will be there regarding the allotment status of this IPO, it will
reach you through Telegram group or video.
So join so that updates can reach you people.
Whatever doubt you have, you
can ask by commenting.  See you in a new Infativa
video.  Till then Jai Hind Jai
Bharat.